orderaheadapp.com 2011-09-26

# OrderAhead - Privacy Policy

← Back Home

Kinetic Farm, Inc. collects certain information through its website, located at www.orderaheadapp.com, and its iPhone app (collectively "OrderAhead"). Your privacy is important to Kinetic Farm, Inc. and this Privacy Policy lays out Kinetic Farm, Inc.'s policies and procedures surrounding the collection and handling of such information. This Privacy Policy applies only to OrderAhead. It does not apply to any restaurant sites, other third party services linked to OrderAhead or offline activities related to Kinetic Farm Inc.'s services.

### Information Kinetic Farm, Inc. Collects

Kinetic Farm, Inc. may collect the following information from users of OrderAhead: first name, last name, street address, city, state, zip code, cross streets, phone number, e-mail address, display name, GPS location and credit card information (collectively, "Personally Identifiable Information" or "PII"). OrderAhead is not intended for use by children under the age of 13 and Kinetic Farm, Inc. does not knowingly collect PII from children under the age of 13.

In addition, Kinetic Farm, Inc. may collect information regarding OrderAhead account holders' past OrderAhead orders, favorite restaurants, customer service inquiries and certain social networking preferences.

Kinetic Farm, Inc. also uses web analytics software to track and analyze traffic on OrderAhead in connection with Kinetic Farm, Inc.'s advertising and promotion of OrderAhead services. Kinetic Farm, Inc. may publish these statistics or share them with third parties without including PII.

### Kinetic Farm, Inc.'s Use Of Collected Information

Kinetic Farm, Inc. uses PII to create users' OrderAhead accounts, to communicate with users about OrderAhead services, to offer users additional services, promotions and special offers and to charge for purchases made through OrderAhead. Users may opt to allow OrderAhead to store certain PII used to create users' OrderAhead accounts, including, but not limited to, credit card information. Kinetic Farm, Inc. uses stored PII to customize future order processing for you. You may request that Kinetic Farm, Inc. cease storing certain PII at any time, but you might not be able to take advantage of certain customized features. Kinetic Farm, Inc. may also use PII to enforce OrderAhead terms of use and service.

Kinetic Farm, Inc. may use cookies to remember users of OrderAhead and to enhance users' experience on the Sites. For example, when users with OrderAhead accounts return to OrderAhead, cookies may be used to identify those users and allow OrderAhead to provide certain user-specific information such as OrderAhead account information, past orders and favorite restaurants.

Kinetic Farm, Inc. shares collected PII to third-party vendors and service providers with whom Kinetic Farm, Inc. works in connection with OrderAhead services. In addition, Kinetic Farm, Inc. shares users' OrderAhead order content, special order instructions, first and last name, location and telephone number with restaurants where users' orders are placed to the extent necessary to process those orders. Kinetic Farm, Inc. may also disclose PII to third parties such as attorneys, collection agencies, tribunals or law enforcement authorities pursuant to valid requests in connection with alleged violations of OrderAhead terms of use and service or other alleged contract violations, infringement or similar harm to persons or property.

Kinetic Farm, Inc. cannot ensure the privacy of any PII included in user generated content that may be enabled by OrderAhead in the future (such as social networking preferences: e.g. "Likes").

### Kinetic Farm, Inc.'s Protection of PII

Kinetic Farm, Inc. uses reasonable security measures to protect PII from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification and disclosure. Unfortunately, even with these measures, Kinetic Farm, Inc. cannot guarantee the security of PII. By using OrderAhead, you acknowledge and agree that Kinetic Farm, Inc. makes no such guarantee, and that you use OrderAhead at your own risk.

### Accessing and Correcting Your PII

Registered OrderAhead account holders can access and change their own PII. If you have questions regarding Kinetic Farm, Inc.'s use or collection of your PII, please contact Kinetic Farm, Inc. at: [admin@kineticfarm.com](mailto:admin@kineticfarm.com).

### Privacy Policy Amendments

Kinetic Farm, Inc. may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new version on this page or on a successor page. The new version will become effective on the posting date, which is listed below as the effective date.

Effective Date: September 14, 2011  ·  Copyright © 2011 Kinetic Farm, Inc., All Rights Reserved.
